He left no time to regret
Kept his dick wet
With his same old safe bet
Me
and my head high
And my tears dry
Get on without my guy
You
went back to what you knew
So far removed
From all that we went through
And I
tread a troubled track
My odds are stacked
I'll go back to black
We only said goodbye with words
I died a hundred times
You go back to her
And I go back to
I go back to us
I love you much
It's not enough
You love blow and I love puff
And life
is like a pipe
And I'm a tiny penny
Rolling up the walls inside
We only said goodbye with words
I died a hundred times
You go back to her
And I go back to
We only said goodbye with words
<br>
I died a hundred times
You go back to her
And I go back to
Black,
black
Black
I go back to
We only said goodbye with words
I died a hundred times
You go back to her
And I go back to
We only said goodbye with words
I died a hundred times
You go back to her
And I go back to black